<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="], // Set tracesSampleRate to 1.0 to capture 100% // of transactions for performance monitoring. // We recommend adjusting this value in production" />
      <item value="void" />
      <item value="** * Call velocity on one or more elements. * * @param elements An `Element`, or an array-like list of `Elements` to * process. * @param propertyMap The `key: value` property map to animate to, or a * named sequence to use. * @param options The options to apply to the animation. This overrides the * default and any supplied in a sequence. */" />
      <item value="property Map" />
      <item value="optimize internal component instantiation // since dynamic options merging is pretty slow, and none of the // internal component options needs special treatment." />
      <item value="is" />
      <item value="they" />
      <item value="An abstraction for an entry managed by a Navigator. This class defines an abstract interface between the navigator and the &quot;routes&quot; that are pushed on and popped off the navigator. Most routes have visual affordances, which they place in the navigators Overlay using one or more OverlayEntry objects. See Navigator for more explanation of how to use a Route with navigation, including code examples. See MaterialPageRoute for a route that replaces the entire screen with a platform-adaptive transition. A route can belong to a page if the settings are a subclass of Page. A page-based route, as opposed to a pageless route, is created from Page.createRoute during Navigator.pages updates. The page associated with this route may change during the lifetime of the route. If the Navigator updates the page of this route, it calls changedInternalState to notify the route that the page has been updated. The type argument T is the route's return type, as used by currentResult, popped, and didPop. The type void may be used if the route does not return a value" />
      <item value="Check" />
      <item value="due" />
      <item value="active Subject Data" />
      <item value="status" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="CHINESE" value="7" />
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="8" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
</application>